<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pato Diaz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pato Diaz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:17:09 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Pi to Sky: How My Kubernetes Cluster Evolved Beyond Raspberry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/from-pi-to-ski/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:17:09 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/from-pi-to-ski/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;from-pi-to-sky-how-my-kubernetes-cluster-evolved-beyond-raspberry&#34;&gt;From Pi to Sky: How My Kubernetes Cluster Evolved Beyond Raspberry&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also published at &lt;a href=&#34;https://dev.to/padiazg/from-pi-to-sky-how-my-kubernetes-cluster-evolved-beyond-raspberry-nf2&#34;&gt;dev.to&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever embarked on a project that seemed straightforward at first, only to find yourself tumbling down a rabbit hole of challenges and discoveries? That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what happened when I decided to breathe new life into my ageing Kubernetes cluster. What began as a simple upgrade turned into an odyssey through the world of single-board computers, operating systems, and DIY ingenuity.
It all started a few years ago with a Raspberry Pi 2, four Raspberry Pi Zeros, and a cluster hat from 8086.net. Little did I know that this modest setup would lead me on a journey spanning multiple hardware platforms, wrestling with ARM architectures, and ultimately crafting my own solutions to keep my cluster alive and kicking.
In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll take you through the twists and turns of my cluster resurrection project. From the initial roadblocks of discontinued support to the thrill of discovering alternative hardware, and finally, to the satisfaction of creating custom solutions. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a fellow tinkerer, a Kubernetes enthusiast, or simply curious about the world of single-board computing, buckle up – this tale of perseverance and problem-solving might just inspire your next tech adventure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
